National Archives and Records Service Copies of Federal Documentation on Black Workers 5584
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- U.S. Department of Labor. Lawrence A. Oxley. State Employment Service State Files. (Box 19)
  - Tennessee - Survey -, 1936-1937 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    Report on the relationship between the Tennessee State Employment Service and Black job applicants. Statistics on population, emergency relief recipients, occupations, local industry and job applicants and employee placements from the Service, divided by race for Nashville and Tennessee.
  - Texas - Centennial -, 1936 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    Correspondence concerning an exhibit by the Labor Department which portrays American workers including Blacks at the Texas Centennial.
  - Texas - Complaints -, 1937 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    Answer to a complaint of discrimination against Blacks.
  - Texas - General Correspondence -, 1937-1939 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    Correspondence arranging conference on Black employment with the Texas State Employment Service. Alleged racial discrimination in staffing by the Service.
  - Texas - Survey -, 1936-1939 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    Report on the relationship between the Texas State Employment Service and Black job applicants. Statistics on population, emergency relief recipients, occupations, local industry, and job applicants and employee placements from the Service divided by race for Texas. Report on field trip to the Service.
  - Virginia - Complaints -, 1937-1939 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    Correspondence alleging discrimination against Blacks by the Virginia State Employment Service in civil service competitive examinations. Black job applicants requesting aid in securing employment.
  - Virginia - General Correspondence -, 1937-1939 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    Correspondence arranging conference on Black employment with the Virginia State Employment Service. Black job applicants requesting aid in securing employment.
  - Virginia - Survey -, 1937-1939 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    Statistics on population, emergency relief recipients, occupations and job applicants and employee placements from the Virginia State Employment Service divided by race for Richmond and Virginia. Editorial describing discrimination against Blacks under the New Deal.
  - Washington, DC - Complaints -, 1935-1937 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    Letters protesting replacement of incompetent B lack worker with unsympathetic white worker at the Washington, DC Employment Service.
  - Washington, DC - General Correspondence -, 1934-1939 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    Conference on the problems of vocational and secondary schools.
  - Washington, DC - Board of Public Welfare -, 1937-1938 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    Correspondence arranging meeting with the Board of Public Welfare to discuss Black problems.
  - Washington, DC - Survey -, 1937-1938 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    Includes racial statistics on population, emergency relief recipients, occupations, unemployment, job applicants and employee placements from the Washington, DC employment service. Report on the relationship between the service and Black job applicants. Discrimination against a Black employee at the Service is alleged.
  - Virginia - Complaints -, 1938 (Box 19, Folder 17)
    Replies to letters alleging discrimination against Blacks.
  - West Virginia - General Correspondence -, 1936-1938 (Box 19, Folder 18)
    Black job applicants requesting aid in securing employment. Discrimination against Blacks in staffing at the West Virginia State Employment Service.
  - West Virginia - Survey -, 1936-1938 (Box 19, Folder 19)
    Report on the relationship between the West Virginia State Employment Service and Black job applicants. Statistics on population, emergency relief recipients, occupations, local industry, unemployment, and on job applicants and employee placements from the service divided by race for Charlestown and West Virginia. Paper on Black families concerning composition, children and employability.
- U.S. Department of Labor. Lawrence A. Oxley Files. Employment Service, Information and Job Applicants Files. (Box 20)
  - A-Y, 1934-1939 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    Includes routine correspondence requesting statistical data, pamphlets, department bulletins, bibliographies, and studies re Black labor. Filed alphabetically by correspondent.
  - A-Y, 1934-1939 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - A-Y, 1934-1939 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - A-Y, 1934-1939 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - A-Y, 1934-1939 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - A-Y, 1934-1939 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - A-Y, 1934-1939 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - A-Y, 1934-1939 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - A-Y, 1934-1939 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - A-Y, 1934-1939 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - A-Y, 1934-1939 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - A-Y, 1934-1939 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - A-Y, 1934-1939 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - A-Y, 1934-1939 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - A-Y, 1934-1939 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - A-Y, 1934-1939 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - A-Y, 1934-1939 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - A-Y, 1934-1939 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - A-Y, 1934-1939 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - A-Y, 1934-1939 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - A-Y, 1934-1939 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - A-Y, 1934-1939 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - A-Y, 1934-1939 (Box 20, Folder 23)
- U.S. Department of Labor. Lawrence A. Oxley Files. Employment Service, Information and Job Applicants Files. (Box 21)
  - A-Y (Section II), 1934-1938 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    Includes routine correspondence and completed application forms of job applicants. Filed alphabetically by applicant.
  - A-Y Section II, 1934-1938 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    Includes correspondence and completed application forms of job applicants. Filed alphabetically by applicant.
  - A-Y Section II, 1934-1938 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - A-Y Section II, 1934-1938 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - A-Y Section II, 1934-1938 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - A-Y Section II, 1934-1938 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - A-Y Section II, 1934-1938 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - A-Y Section II, 1934-1938 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - A-Y Section II, 1934-1938 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - A-Y Section II, 1934-1938 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - A-Y Section II, 1934-1938 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - A-Y Section II, 1934-1938 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - A-Y Section II, 1934-1938 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - A-Y Section II, 1934-1938 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - A-Y Section II, 1934-1938 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - A-Y Section II, 1934-1938 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - A-Y Section II, 1934-1938 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - A-Y Section II, 1934-1938 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - A-Y Section II, 1934-1938 (Box 21, Folder 19)
- Karl F. Phillips. Commissioner of Conciliation. Files. (Box 22)
  - Andrews, R. McCants - Durham, NC attorney, invites Phillips to various functions., 1925 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Beckett, Bishop W.W. - Mississippi - Requests DOL aid for project, 1925 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Beckwith, Frank R. - Indiana, Director of Negro Welfare, requests of Phillips for job, 1929-1932 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Branch, Joel P. - Cleveland - Hand-written report on labor situation for Blacks., 1925 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Bruce, Phillip A. - University of Virginia, send Phillips monograph on northward migration of Blacks., 1924 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Bruseaux, Sheridan A. - Chicago, Principal Keystone National Detective Agency, Incorporated, requests information on employment situation for Blacks all over United States., 1925-1928 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Burton, James D. - Georgia, Interstate Secretary for Alabama and Tennessee, Commission on Interracial Cooperation, requesting information on miners wages., 1926 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Campbell, Charles C. - Michigan, Lansing, Special Industrial Agent for DOL, requests information farming, migration of Blacks., 1924-1926 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Chisum, Melvin J. - DC Field Secretary, National Negro Press Association, thanking Phillips for getting friend a job., 1925 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Clark, John L. - Pittsburgh, Printer, request Phillips aid to guard against discrimination by International Typographical Union - Phillips suggests taking matter up with Charles Howard, International President., 1927 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Cobb, Robert S. - Jefferson City, Missouri, Executive Secretary of Negro Industrial Commission requests Phillips aid in finding job., 1925 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Commerce Department - compilation of statistics on persons in jail by race., 1923 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - D.C. and New York - one female requests Phillips to get $15 due her for work as cook, 1 other requests help in clothing trades and general correspondence., 1927-1930 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Copeland, M.L. - Kentucky, routine., 1925 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Cotton Picking Machine - Department of Labor, news release about new machine; requests for information from many farmers., 1931 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Crabmeat Pickers - Maryland, pickers go on strike since their wages dropped from 35 cents to 25 cents., 1931 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Davidson, Lucy E. - DC, letter to Kerwin thanking him for recommending that she be allowed to keep her job., 1929 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - DePriest, Honorable Oscar - D.C., Congressman, calls non-partisan conference on Blacks; correspondence re Brotherhood of Railway Trainmen dispute., 1929-1931 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Dining Car Waiters - Lemus, Rienzi B., ask for same hours and benefits as other railroad union members., 1926 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Elks (Wilson) D.C., request Secretary Davis to send them U United States Health representative as speaker., 1929 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Employment - Howard University, bricklayers discriminated against in wages; United States confidential reports on Black unemployment, 1926- 1928 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Employment Service Plan - Indiana, Phillips successful in helping employ Black man; letter from another describing Black emancipation., 1931- 1932 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Employment Service - Special - requests to Phillips for aid in finding jobs., 1931 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Ernst, Senator R.P. - Kentucky, routine., 1926 (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Fite, Hadley G. - Indiana, trying to keep Bureau for Blacks open., 1925-1927 (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - Francis, Rothschild - Virgin Islands, Administrator seeks information from Phillips; news article on prevailing wage., 1925-1926 (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - Froe, Arthur G. - D.C., recorder of deeds, requests Phillips for information to send to friends re Blacks., 1927 (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - Furr, Arthur F. - D.C., requests Phillips to help him get a job., 1925 (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - Goens, Walter W. - New York, requests Phillips aid in getting certified as a doctor and finding employment., 1927 (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - Governorship - Pennsylvania, Phillips acts as Secretary Labor Davis' campaign manager of Black vote., 1929-1930 (Box 22, Folder 30)
  - Harris, Professor Abram - Request for information on Black migration., 1925 (Box 22, Folder 31)
  - Hale, W.J. Request for Georgia Douglas to speak at a conference in Tennessee., 1927 (Box 22, Folder 32)
  - Hall, Seabron F. - Detroit, letter of friendship and reply., 1925 (Box 22, Folder 33)
  - Harris, George W. Request for job, report on Black labor statistics, Peoria, Illinois., 1925-1927 (Box 22, Folder 34)
  - Haynes, George E. Executive Secretary of Interracial Conference asks Davis to participate and routine., 1928 (Box 22, Folder 35)
  - Henning, E.J., New York - requests aid in finding employment for a friend., 1930 (Box 22, Folder 36)
  - Henry, Judge Edward - Answer from Phillips to request for Labor Department's aid with conciliation., 1924 (Box 22, Folder 37)
  - Hert, Alvin F. (Mrs.) Republican National Committee requests Phillips aid in finding a job for wife of late Phil Brown., 1924 (Box 22, Folder 38)
  - Hill, Honorable T. Edwards - West Virginia, Director of Negro Welfare and Statistics, aids Phillips with reports, requests job with Phillips., 1925 (Box 22, Folder 39)
  - Howard, Honorable Perry W. - Requests Phillips help in naturalizing immigrants., 1928-1930 (Box 22, Folder 40)
  - Howard Theatre Dispute - Dispute on Howard Theatre's musician dispute., 1926 (Box 22, Folder 41)
  - Immigration - Princeton University, 82 page report on immigration from Latin America and West Indies to America., 1930 (Box 22, Folder 42)
  - Indiana - Cases - Dynes, Commissioner in Indiana, sends friends to Phillips for employment; talks about political situation., 1930-1931 (Box 22, Folder 43)
  - Industrial Trends - Black migration, social adjustments, employment problems, attitudes., 1926-1929 (Box 22, Folder 44)
  - Johnson, Charles S., Research Director for National Interracial Conference asks Phillips for studies on Blacks to secure accurate picture of current Black living., 1928 (Box 22, Folder 45)
  - Johnson, J.R. - Black from Texas requests Phillips aid in finding information on building and loan associations., 1929 (Box 22, Folder 46)
  - Johnson, Sol - Commissioner of Immigration at Ellis Island., 1925 (Box 22, Folder 47)
  - Jones, Eugene Kinckle - Executive Secretary of national Urban League, re favors and recommendations., 1924-1926 (Box 22, Folder 48)
  - Jones, Francis I. - Director General, United States Employment Service, request for information re employment., 1925-1926 (Box 22, Folder 49)
  - Jones, Scipio - Masonic Order, noted Black lawyer and judge asks Phillips help in raising funds for needy youth and the elderly., 1925- 1926 (Box 22, Folder 50)
  - Lewis, Morris - Chicago, Commissioner of Conciliation, routine correspondence, 1924-1930 (Box 22, Folder 51)
  - Mailing List - routine, 1927 (Box 22, Folder 52)
  - McCracken, Fred D. - personal friend of Phillips, requests aid in establishment of job., 1925-1928 (Box 22, Folder 53)
  - McDougald, G.E. (Mrs.) - Harlem Vocational Guidance Committee, joint report with DOL., 1925 (Box 22, Folder 54)
  - Miller, Kelly - Howard University, "The Farm: The Negroes Best Chance," and requests for information., 1925-1926 (Box 22, Folder 55)
  - Morrison, Julia - Request for information, 1925 (Box 22, Folder 56)
  - Negro Colonization of Africa - correspondence., 1933 (Box 22, Folder 57)
  - Negro Labor Congress - Militant news clippings, 1925 (Box 22, Folder 58)
  - Nelms, H.G. - Alabama, Obscure union official, requesting information., 1929-1930 (Box 22, Folder 59)
  - Paxton, A.M. - Requests information on Black occupational survey., 1924-1925 (Box 22, Folder 60)
  - Penny, Theodore R. - Pennsylvania, man with plan on home life. Phillips arranges interview between him and Governor Pinchet of Pennsylvania., 1926 (Box 22, Folder 61)
  - Pennsylvania Railroad - menu., 1929 (Box 22, Folder 62)
  - Peters, Robert J. - Pennsylvania Director of Employment Bureau, Phillips requests statistics from their office., 1925 (Box 22, Folder 63)
  - Press Release - Race Pride versus Profit and Old Age Pension (Negro Labor News Service), 1929 (Box 22, Folder 64)
  - Prevailing Rate Legislation, 1931 (Box 22, Folder 65)
  - Prevailing Rate Legislation - Virginia, 1931 (Box 22, Folder 66)
  - Railway Workers - Indiana, reinstatement case of a woman who may have falsified age, recommendation from Phillips to Secretary of Labor to make railroad crimes a federal offense., 1932 (Box 22, Folder 67)
  - Requests - for literature on Blacks, 1927-1928 (Box 22, Folder 68)
  - Robins, James J. - Letters of thanks to Phil Brown and Phillips for aid in finding employment., 1925 (Box 22, Folder 69)
  - Rosenthal, Aaron M. - "The Negro Problem", 1924-1925 (Box 22, Folder 70)
  - Schields, R.G. - aid in securing appointment., 1925-1926 (Box 22, Folder 71)
  - Scott, Emmett J. - Secretary-Treasurer, Howard University, requests for jobs., 1926-1929 (Box 22, Folder 72)
  - Scruggs, Baxter S. - Director, YMCA Detroit, requests Phillips to find job, then gets job with YMCA and wants to coordinate efforts with DOL., 1924- 1926 (Box 22, Folder 73)
  - Shepard, J.E. - President, North Carolina College for Negroes - re program for 3rd Annual Fact Finding Conference., 1930 (Box 22, Folder 74)
  - Sherard, Thomas W. - job applicant., 1925 (Box 22, Folder 75)
  - Simpson, Gordon H. - mailing list request., 1927 (Box 22, Folder 76)
  - Sledge, Wesley L. - Executive Secretary, Republican National Committee, Routine, 1926 (Box 22, Folder 77)
  - Smallwood, William H. - job applicant., 1929 (Box 22, Folder 78)
  - Smith, Olander J. - friend and job applicant., 1927-1929 (Box 22, Folder 79)
  - Social Welfare - Phillips gets prison inmate job after his release., 1928-1929 (Box 22, Folder 80)
  - Spurlock, Anna (Compensation) - re widow of deceased Carnegie Steel Company employee, denied., 1928 (Box 22, Folder 81)
  - Stokes, Harold Phelps - re report on Blacks on steam railway lines., 1925 (Box 22, Folder 82)
  - Surveys - Report by Phillips distributed without permission of DOL; statistics on Black workers from Ohio; report on fact finding committee; re Mexico restricts Blacks from immigrating., 1924-1931 (Box 22, Folder 83)
  - Tennessee Coal Iron and Railroad Company - spring festival for children in school., 1925 (Box 22, Folder 84)
  - Thomas, James C. - re immigration questions., 1930-1931 (Box 22, Folder 85)
  - Thompson, A.B. - President, National Association of Railway Mechanics, re request information on Railroad Mediation Board., 1926 (Box 22, Folder 86)
  - Travel - routine travel authorizations., 1925-1931 (Box 22, Folder 87)
  - Trigg, J.M. Job applicant., 1925 (Box 22, Folder 88)
  - Tuskegee - re summer lectures., 1929 (Box 22, Folder 89)
  - Unemployment - Congress, article from "Congressional Record", 1931 (Box 22, Folder 90)
  - Urban League - re employment, Negroes; Boulder Dam employing Blacks; Survey of laundry workers; reports on industry., 1924-1931 (Box 22, Folder 91)
  - Vann, Robert L. - Phillips thanks editor, Pittsburgh Courier, for favorable write-up on Secretary Davis., 1925 (Box 22, Folder 92)
  - Virgin Islands - report of Federal Commission to investigate industrial and economic conditions in the Virgin Islands and routine correspondence., 1924-1927 (Box 22, Folder 93)
  - Vocational Studies - New York - request for information on Black workers., 1931 (Box 22, Folder 94)
  - Wages - Pullman Porters - news clippings re tips; petition from Brotherhood of Sleeping Car Porters and Pullman Company to ICC to prevent tipping., 1925-1933 (Box 22, Folder 95)
  - Whitney, J.R.B. - job applicant., 1925 (Box 22, Folder 96)
  - Warfield, William A. - reference for a steno-typist., 1926 (Box 22, Folder 97)
  - Walrond, Eric D. re review of article on Virgin Islands; editorials from "Opportunity.", 1925 (Box 22, Folder 98)
  - Ward, Colonel Joseph H. - Director of Virginia Hospital at Tuskegee Institute re assisting a disabled vet from Indiana., 1927-1928 (Box 22, Folder 99)
  - Washington, Forrester B. - Director, Atlanta School of Social Work re requests for information, materials and favors., 1924-1928 (Box 22, Folder 100)
  - Webb, C. Cornelius - Phillips congratulating Webb on appointment as special investigator and mediator for Pullman Company., 1925 (Box 22, Folder 101)
  - Welfare Department - article, "The Need of the Nation.", 1925 (Box 22, Folder 102)
  - White House (Social) - re Blacks as guests at the White House; newspaper clippings., 1929-1930 (Box 22, Folder 103)
  - Williams, Georgia - request for information., 1925-1926 (Box 22, Folder 104)
  - Wilson, Robert E. Lee - re annual report of the Secretary of Labor., 1926 (Box 22, Folder 105)
  - Woodson, George H. - re job applicant of position of Minister to the Republic of Liberia., 1926-1927 (Box 22, Folder 106)
  - Women's Activities - Publication "Causes of Absence for Men and Women in Four Cotton Mills;" National Association of Colored Women Conference re planning for program; studies and activities of Black women in industry., 1929-1931 (Box 22, Folder 107)
  - Wright, Eva A. - re instruction of colored women in voting, by Republican Women's Club., 1924 (Box 22, Folder 108)
  - Wright, R.R. - requests information on Black labor., 1928 (Box 22, Folder 109)
  - Young, Adele - loss of money order, 1929 (Box 22, Folder 110)
- Division of Negro Economics. Files. (Box 23)
  - Includes correspondence, memos and statements describing the function and creation of the Division of Negro Economics; clippings and question and answer mimeo re the Division and Negro industrial interests., 1918-1921 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - re staffing suggestions; appointments; re publication, "Negro-Migration, 1916-1917;" meetings; plans; colored labor of the south; conditions of war workers; Negro Economics in Ohio; and routine., 1918 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - re conferences; furlough of Forrester B. Washington to work for Division; staffing; cooperation with United State Employment Service; question of discrimination within the Department; minutes, 10/23/18; and routine., 1918 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - re Negro wage earners; staffing; resolutions' publishing a bulletin; meetings and routine., 1919 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - re William Jennifer discharge due to lack of funds; transfer of Jennifer and Charles Hall; Negroes in Industry; condition of colored situation in the south; and routine., 1919 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - re mortality among Negro children; Negro women workers; financial; meetings; "The Racial Question," speech by Senator Selden P. Spencer (Missouri), 5/22/20; publication of a department bulletin; comparison of incomes of Blacks and whites in similar indust, 1920 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - re staffing; re publications of "The Negro at Work During the War and Reconstruction;" questionnaire; Negro from colonies; adjustment of work of Charles Hall and William Jennifer, Special Agents; and routine., 1920 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - re functions and work of Negro Economics Advisory Service; and routine., 1921 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - 3 page mimeo entitled "Negro Economics in Florida," no date. (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Financial papers, includes estimated budget for 1918-1919 and related documents. (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - "Matters of Record" - details functions and organization of the Division., 1918-1919 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - "Program of Work" and "Preliminary Programs" - outline of programs of conferences; outline of work plans of the Division. (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - "Reports" - includes reports on various subjects; "Negro Migration Report;" interview with Senator Fletcher of Florida; reports of weekly and monthly activities of the Division; compulsory work law; reports on various localities; Negro Economics in Florid, 1919-1920 (Box 23, Folder 13)
- Division of Negro Economics. Files. (Box 24)
  - A- with American Unity Labor Union re discrimination of Blacks in labor unions; with G.W. Austin Vice-President Brotherhood of Shop Laborer's re organization of Blacks in southern states; "The Armenia America Society," 2 page mimeo; letters recommending v, 1918-1921 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - B - Letters of recommendation from various sources for positions in the Division; with T.W. Bickett, Governor of North Carolina; with Clara H. Blackman of St. Petersburg Times., 1918-1921 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - C - with Chicago League on Urban Conditions Among Negroes re cooperation with Mr. Washington, Supervisor of Negro Economics in Illinois and the Chicago League; with Cleveland Poll Survey Committee to W.B. Wilson, Secretary of Labor re southern railroad wo, 1918-1924 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Carter, Jeanette, President of the Woman's Wage Earner's Association re letters of recommendation for position with Department of Labor's Housing Bureau, her appointment and later removal from the position., 1918 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Council of National Defense - correspondence with Governor Clarkson, Division of the Council re the formation of a Committee of Negroes under the Council; migration of Negroes from south to the north., 1917-1918 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - D - re "Dillard Report" on Negro labor exodus from the southern states., 1918 (Box 24, Folder 6)